[Music]
hey
how you doing it's friends this ice
cream serendipity
they i mean historically they made some
pretty crap ice creams
but they've got an agreement with a tv
production company movie
production company to make some famous
flavors related to
film and tv goonies one they've done
we'll deal with that another time
and there's some others that they are
doing that haven't come out yet so when
they come out we'll have a look at those
as well but today
is all about friends the friends reunion
came out last week everyone's rushing to
see it
we are also rushing to see it let's
look at what it is it's a coffee ice
cream with
fudge swirl and dark chocolate covered
almonds
all sounds pretty simple let's just get
stuck in and make it
we're going to make a custard base this
time but instead of tempering eggs in
the traditional way we're just going to
heat them all up into the pan up to
82 degrees centigrade 8285 degrees
something like that
add your milk cream sugar and find your
eggs and get them up to that temperature
gently
then add your coffee powder give it a
good stir to dissolve
finally turn the heat off and add your
vanilla extract i'm actually making some
of my own at the moment so
watch this space in a year to 18 months
when it comes to back of a spoon sling
it in a container and chill in the
fridge for 4 hours
[Music]
the fudge is my dairy milk fudge so melt
your chocolate and butter in a microwave
and whisk your egg and sugar together
combine all of this and it's ready to go
just pop it in a container in the fridge
it won't pour straight from the fridge
so you might want to heat up just a
little bit if you want to pour it in
[Music]
when your ice cream is ready to churn
get it in and prepare your nuts
[Music]
chop them however you want and put them
aside i've left some large and small
pieces here
[Music]
then finally load it all into your
container and don't skimp on the fudge
and nuts
freeze it for a few hours until you're
ready to eat it
[Music]
the ice cream's been in the freezer for
quite a while now to 24 hours-ish
we're going to get some out into the
bowl and see what it looks like
[Music]
so it scoops really well i mean you
smell the coffee coming out of it it's
it's
really strong i mean i have made this
pretty strong coffee wise and that's
something that someone did review online
they said that the coffee flavor was
really weak and pathetic
and there wasn't really much of a fudge
swirl in there so
i guess if you're trying to make a big
comeback after not doing particularly
well
with your ice creams go bold you know
put the whole lot in
make a statement about it i mean you're
using friends as
the main kind of tag for your ice cream
so
make it a good one you know
[Music]
that is really good
that's amazing even if i do say so
myself
coffee ice cream you're gonna get a rush
from that
there's some serious caffeine in there
the fudge well
i use this fudge well a lot it's a dairy
milk fudge well so it's got a really
good taste to it
soft scoopable doesn't go hard in the
freezer
dark chocolate covered almonds they're
not like
you know bullets like a lot of chocolate
is
just a nice bit of crunch
overall it's a real winning combination
but it is surprising and easy to make
coffee ice cream you can make it however
you like some people soak the beans
some people use instant like i have here
use whatever you want custard base
philly style doesn't make any difference
just make a good
coffee ice cream put some of those dark
chocolate covered almonds in
add in your fudge swirl get it in a
container
go for it it's a really good
combination of flavors i'm gonna eat
this whole thing and maybe some more
i hope you enjoyed this one nice and
simple thanks for watching i hope you
like and subscribe and we'll see you
next time